Guide to the Stanford University, Press, Archival Book Copies
Stanford University. Libraries.
- 1998
  - Derrida, Jacques, Resistances of psychoanalysis., 1998 (Box 4)
  - Duffield, John S, World power forsaken: political culture, international institutions, and German security policy after unification., 1998 (Box 5)
  - Durham, Scott, 1960-, Phantom communities: the simulacrum and the limits of postmodernism., 1998 (Box 5)
  - Dye, Alan, 1958-, Cuban sugar in the age of mass production: technology and the economics of the sugar central, 1899-1929., 1998 (Box 5)
  - Estabrook, Carl B., Urbane and rustic England: cultural ties and social spheres in the provinces 1660-1780., 1998 (Box 5)
  - Ferrell, Lori Anne, 1957-, Government by Polemic: James I, the king's preachers, and the rhetorics of conformity, 1603-1625., 1998 (Box 5)
  - Feuerwerker, Yi-tsi Mei, 1928-, Ideology, power, text: self-representation and the peasant "other" in modern Chinese literature Press, 1998. (Box 5)
  - Flint, Christopher, 1957-, Family fictions: narrative and domestic relations in Britain, 1688-1798., 1998 (Box 5)
  - Froment-Meurice, Marc, That is--to say: Heidegger's poetics; translated by Jan Plug., 1998 (Box 5)
  - Giddens, Anthony, Conversations with Anthony Giddens: making sense of modernity., 1998 (Box 5)
  - Gilman, Sander L, Love+marriage=death: and other essays on representing difference., 1998 (Box 6)
  - Gladney, Dru C., editor, Making majorities: constituting the nation in Japan, Korea, China, Malaysia, Fiji, Turkey, and the United States., 1998 (Box 6)
  - Goodby, James E, Europe undivided: the new logic of peace in U.S.-Russian., 1998 (Box 6)
  - Goux, Jean-Joseph and Philip R. Wood, editors, Terror and consensus: vicissitudes of French thought., 1998 (Box 6)
  - Graham, Loren R, What have we learned about science and technology from the Russian experience? 1998. (Box 6)
  - Greaves, Richard L, Dublin's merchant-Quaker: Anthony Sharp and the Community of Friends, 1643-1707., 1998 (Box 6)
  - Hale, Dorothy J, Social formalism: the novel in theory from Henry James to the present., 1998 (Box 6)
  - Hamacher, Werner, Pleroma: reading in Hegel: the genesis and structure of a dialectial hermeneutics in Hegel., 1998 (Box 6)
  - Hegel, Robert E., 1943-, Reading illustrated fiction in late imperial China., 1998 (Box 6)
  - Hopkins, James K., 1941-, Into the heart of the fire: the British in the Spanish Civil War., 1998 (Box 6)
  - Huffer, Lynne, Maternal pasts, feminist futures: nostalgia, ethics, and the question of difference., 1998 (Box 7)
  - Ikeda, Keiko, A room full of mirrors: high school reunions in middle America., 1998 (Box 7)
  - Israel, John, 1935-, Lianda: a Chinese university in war and revolution., 1998 (Box 7)
  - Jones, Grant D., 1941-, The conquest of the last Maya kingdom., 1998 (Box 7)
  - Katz, Friedrich, The life and times of Pancho Villa., 1998 (Box 7)
  - Keane, John, 1949-, Civil society: old images, new visions., 1998 (Box 7)
  - Larson, Wendy, Women and writing in modern China., 1998 (Box 7)
  - Lasso de la Vega, Luis, 17th cent, The story of Guadalupe: Luis Laso de la Vega's Huei tlamahuicoltica of 1649 / edited and translated by Lisa Sousa, Stafford Poole, James Lockhart., 1998 (Box 11)
  - Leclaire, Serge, A child is being killed: on primary narcissism and the death drive., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Leclaire, Serge, Psychoanalyzing: on the order of the unconscious and the practice of the letter., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Lenoir, Timothy, Inscribing science: scientific texts and the materiality of communication., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Levenstein, Margaret, Accounting for growth: information systems and the creation of the large corporation., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Levinas, Emmanuel, Of God - who comes to mind., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Li, David Leiwei, 1959-, Imagining the nation: Asian American literature and cultural consent., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Lie, John, Han unbound: the political economy of South Korea., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Lindenberger, Herbert Samuel, 1929-, Opera in history: from Monteverdi to Cage., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Luhmann, Niklas, Love as passion: the codification of intimacy., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Luhmann, Niklas, Observations on modernity., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Macauley, Melissa Ann, Social power and legal culture: litigation masters in late imperial China., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Masukagami. English, The clear mirror: a chronicle of the Japanese court during the Kamakura period (1185-1333) / translated, with notes and an introduction, by George W. Perkins., 1998 (Box 9)
  - Maurer, Shawn L., 1960-, Proposing men: dialectics of gender and class in the eighteenth-century English periodical., 1998 (Box 9)
  - McCarren, Felicia M, Dance pathologies: performance, poetics, medicine., 1998 (Box 8)
  - McGinty, Brian, Strong wine: the life and legend of Agoston Haraszthy., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Millward, James A., 1961-, Beyond the pass: economy, ethnicity, and empire in Qing Central Asia, 1759-1864., 1998 (Box 9)
  - Niemann, Linda, Railroad voices., 1998 (Box 9)
  - Peltz, Rakhmiel, From immigrant to ethnic culture., 1998 (Box 9)
  - Petrucci, Armando, Writing the dead: death and writing strategies in the Western tradition., 1998 (Box 9)
  - Reynolds, Elaine A, Before the bobbies: the night watch and police reform in metropolitan London, 1720-1830., 1998 (Box 9)
  - Roberts, Kenneth M., 1958-, Deepening democracy?: the modern left and social movements in Chile and Peru., 1998 (Box 9)
  - Roddy, Stephen, Literati identity and its fictional representations in late imperial China., 1998 (Box 10)
  - Ruf, Gregory A, Cadres and kin: making a socialist village in West China, 1921-1991., 1998 (Box 10)
  - Ruttenburg, Nancy, Democratic personality: popular voice and the trial of American authorship., 1998 (Box 10)
  - Sadoff, Dianne F, Sciences of the flesh: representing body and subject in psychoanalysis., 1998 (Box 10)
  - Sankovitch, Natasha, Creating and recovering experience., 1998 (Box 10)
  - Scheiber, Harry N., editor, The state and freedom of contract., 1998 (Box 10)
  - Seminaire de Capri (1994), Religion / edited by Jacques Derrida and Gianni Vattimo., 1998 (Box 4)
  - Shapiro, Gilbert, Revolutionary demands: a content analysis of the Cahiers de doleances of 1789., 1998 (Box 10)
  - Shirane, Haruo, 1951-, Traces of dreams: landscape, cultural memory, and the poetry of Basho., 1998 (Box 10)
  - Simpson, Michael, 1957-, Closet performances: political exhibition and prohibition in the dramas of Byron and Shelley., 1998 (Box 11)
  - Snyder, Susan, Pastoral process: Spenser, Marvell, Milton., 1998 (Box 11)
  - Sommer, Benjamin D., 1964-, A prophet reads scripture: allusion in Isaiah 40-66., 1998 (Box 11)
  - Stiegler, Bernard, Technics and time; translated by Richard Beardsworth and George Collins., 1998 (Box 11)
  - Strauss, Jonathan, Subjects of terror: Nerval, Hegel, and the modern self., 1998 (Box 11)
  - Sturzenhofecker, G. (Gabriele), Times enmeshed: gender, space, and history among the Duna of Papua New Guinea., 1998 (Box 11)
  - Sullivan, Garrett A, The drama of landscape: land, property, and social relations on the early modern stage., 1998 (Box 11)
  - Szelenyi, Szonja, 1960-, Equality by design: the grand experiment in destratification in Socialist Hungary., 1998 (Box 11)
  - Tulchin, Joseph S., et. al, editors, Strategic balance and confidence building measures in the Americas., 1998 (Box 11)
  - Ueda, Makoto, 1931-, The path of flowering thorn: the life and poetry of Yosa Buson 1998. (Box 12)
  - Vanderwood, Paul J, The power of God against the guns of government: religious upheaval in Mexico at the turn of the century., 1998 (Box 12)
  - Vertzberger, Yaacov, Risk taking and decisionmaking: foreign military intervention decisions., 1998 (Box 12)
  - Wachtel, Andrew, Making a nation, breaking a nation: literature and cultural politics in Yugoslavia., 1998 (Box 12)
  - Watkins, Evan, 1946-, Everyday exchanges: marketwork and capitalist common sense., 1998 (Box 12)
  - Watts, Philip, 1961-, Allegories of the purge: how literature responded to the postwar trials of writers and intellectuals in France., 1998 (Box 12)
  - Weiler, Kathleen, Country schoolwomen: teaching in rural California, 1850-1950., 1998 (Box 12)
  - Westad, Odd Arne, editor, Brothers in arms: the rise and fall of the Sino-Soviet alliance, 1945-1963., 1998 (Box 12)
  - Winock, Michel, Nationalism, anti-semitism, and fascism in France., 1998 (Box 12)
  - Wrong, Dennis Hume, 1923-, The modern condition: essays at century's end., 1998 (Box 13)
  - Zhang, Longxi, Mighty opposites: from dichotomies to differences in the comparative study of China., 1998 (Box 13)
  - Zhang, Yingjin, editor,, China in a polycentric world: essays in Chinese comparative literature., 1998 (Box 13)
- 1999
  - Adams, R. J. Q. (Ralph James Q.), 1943-, Bonar Law.., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Adelman, Jeremy, Republic of capital: Buenos Aires and the legal transformation of the Atlantic world., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Adorno, Theodor W., 1903-1969, Sound figures / translated by Rodney Livingstone.., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Agamben, Giorgio, 1942-, Potentialities: collected essays in philosophy / edited and translated with an introduction by Daniel Heller-Roazen.., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Agamben, Giorgio, 1942-, The end of the poem: studies in poetics / translated by Daniel Heller-Roazen.., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Agamben, Giorgio, 1942-, The man without content / translated by Georgia Albert.., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Aisenberg, Andrew Robert, Contagion: disease, government, and the social question in nineteenth-century France., 1999 (Box 2)
  - Arnson, Cynthia J., editor, Comparative peace processes in Latin America., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Auge, Marc, An anthropology for contemporaneous worlds., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Baecker, Dirk, editor., Problems of form., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Bal, Mieke, editor., The practice of cultural analysis: exposing interdisciplinary interpretation., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Barney, Richard A., 1955-, Plots of enlightenment: education and the novel in eighteenth-century England., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Bauman, Zygmunt, In search of politics., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Beale, Marjorie A, The modernist enterprise: French elites and the threat of modernity, 1900-1940., 1999 (Box 2)
  - Bell, Lynda Schaefer, One industry, two Chinas: silk filatures and peasant-family production in Wuxi County, 1865-1937., 1999 (Box 2)
  - Bernhardt, Kathryn., Women and property in China: 960-1949., 1999 (Box 2)
  - Boli, John and George M. Thomas, editors., Constructing world culture: international nongovernmental organizations since 1875., 1999 (Box 2)
  - Bourdieu, Pierre, The weight of the world: social suffering in contemporary society., 1999 (Box 2)
  - Boyarin, Daniel, Dying for God: martyrdom and the making of Christianity and Judaism., 1999 (Box 2)
  - Bronstein, Jamie L., 1968-, Land reform and working-class experience in Britain and the United States, 1800-1862., 1999 (Box 2)
  - Burt, E. S, Poetry's appeal: nineteenth-century French lyric and the political space., 1999 (Box 2)
  - Caron, Vicki, 1951-, Uneasy asylum: France and the Jewish refugee crisis, 1933-1942., 1999 (Box 3)
  - Cha, Victor D., 1961-, Alignment despite antagonism: the United States-Korea-Japan security., 1999 (Box 3)
  - Chang, Kang-i Sun and Haun Saussy, editors, Women writers of traditional China: an anthology of poetry and criticism., 1999 (Box 3)
  - Chesnutt, Charles Waddell, 1858-1932, Charles W. Chesnutt: essays and speeches / edited by Joseph R. McElrath, Jr., Robert C. Leitz III, Jesse S. Crisler.., 1999 (Box 3)
  - Chowning, Margaret, Wealth and power in provincial Mexico: Michoacan from the late colony to the Revolution., 1999 (Box 3)
  - Collins, Randall, 1941-, Macrohistory: essays in sociology of the long run., 1999 (Box 3)
  - Cornyetz, Nina, Dangerous women, deadly words: phallic fantasy and modernity in three Japanese writers., 1999 (Box 3)
  - Cotterrell, Roger (Roger B. M.), Emile Durkheim: law in a moral domain., 1999 (Box 3)
  - Cullather, Nick, 1959-, Secret history: the CIA's classified account of its operations in Guatemala, 1952-1954., 1999 (Box 3)
  - Deutsch, Sandra McGee, 1950-, Las Derechas: the extreme right in Argentina, Brazil, and Chile, 1890-1939., 1999 (Box 3)
  - Dubin, Lois C., 1952-, The port Jews of Habsburg Trieste: absolutist politics and enlightenment culture., 1999 (Box 4)
  - Edelman, Marc, Peasants against globalization: rural social movements in Costa Rica., 1999 (Box 4)
  - Engerman, Stanley L., editor., The terms of labor: slavery, serfdom, and free labor., 1999 (Box 4)
  - Esch, Deborah, 1954-, In the event: reading journalism, reading theory., 1999 (Box 4)
  - Field, Hermann H., 1910-, Trapped in the Cold War: the ordeal of an American family., 1999 (Box 4)
  - Fink, Amir Sumakai and Jacob Press, editors., Independence park: the lives of gay men in Israel., 1999 (Box 4)
  - Fioretos, Aris, The gray book., 1999 (Box 4)
  - Freedman, Paul H., 1949-, Images of the medieval peasant., 1999 (Box 4)
  - Gaubatz, Kurt Taylor, Elections and war: the electoral incentive in the democratic politics of war and peace., 1999 (Box 4)
  - Gitelman, Lisa, Scripts, grooves, and writing machines: representing technology in the Edison era., 1999 (Box 4)
  - Gleason, William A, The leisure ethic: work and play in American literature, 1840-1940., 1999 (Box 12)
  - Graham, Wendy, 1957-, Henry James's thwarted love., 1999 (Box 5)
  - Granich, Reuben, 1963-, HIV, health, and your community: a guide for action., 1999 (Box 5)
  - Gutjahr, Paul C, An American Bible: a history of the Good Book in the United States., 1999 (Box 5)
  - Hamacher, Werner, Premises: essays on philosophy and literature from Kant to Celan., 1999 (Box 5)
  - Hare, Tom, 1952-, ReMembering Osiris: number, gender, and the word in ancient Egyptian representational systems., 1999 (Box 5)
  - Harshav, Benjamin, 1928-, Language in time of revolution., 1999 (Box 5)
  - Harshav, Benjamin, 1928-, The meaning of Yiddish., 1999 (Box 5)
  - Hawkins, Peter S, Dante's testaments: essays on scriptural imagination., 1999 (Box 5)
  - Held, David, Global transformations: politics, economics and culture., 1999 (Box 5)
  - Holderlin, Friedrich, The solid letter: readings of Friedrich Holderlin / edited by Aris Fioretos.., 1999 (Box 5)
  - Irlam, Shaun, 1959-, Elations: the poetics of enthusiasm in eighteenth-century Britain., 1999 (Box 6)
  - Jin, Qiu, 1956-, The culture of power: the Lin Biao incident in the Cultural Revolution., 1999 (Box 9)
  - Kaldor, Mary, New and old wars: organized violence in a global era., 1999 (Box 12)
  - Kittler, Friedrich A, Gramophone, film, typewriter., 1999 (Box 6)
  - Lacoue-Labarthe, Philippe, Poetry as experience., 1999 (Box 6)
  - Leivick, Joel, Carrara: the marble quarries of Tuscany., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Lockhart, James, Of things of the Indies: essays old and new in early Latin American history., 1999 (Box 6)
  - London, Jack, 1876-1916, No mentor but myself: Jack London on writers and writings / edited by Dale L. Walker and Jeanne Campbell Reesman., 1999 (Box 6)
  - Lubman, Stanley B., 1934-, Bird in a cage: legal reform in China after Mao., 1999 (Box 6)
  - Lynch, Daniel C, After the propaganda state: media, politics, and "thought work" in reformed China., 1999 (Box 6)
  - Macauley, Melissa Ann, Social power and legal culture: litigation masters in late imperial China., 1999 (Box 6)
  - Mainwaring, Scott, 1954-, Rethinking party systems in the third wave of democratization: the case of Brazil., 1999 (Box 7)
  - Malcolmson, Cristina, Heart-work: George Herbert and the Protestant ethic., 1999 (Box 7)
  - Maleuvre, Didier, Museum memories: history, technology, art., 1999 (Box 7)
  - Marin, Louis, 1931-, Sublime Poussin / Louis Marin; translated by Catherine Porter., 1999 (Box 7)
  - Marquez, Patricia C., 1965-, The street is my home: youth and violence in Caracas., 1999 (Box 7)
  - Martel, Frédéric, 1967-, The pink and the black: homosexuals in France since 1968., 1999 (Box 7)
  - Mass, Jeffrey P, Yoritomo and the founding of the first Bakufu: the origins of dual government in Japan., 1999 (Box 7)
  - McClendon, Muriel C, The quiet Reformation: magistrates and the emergence of Protestantism in Tudor Norwich., 1999 (Box 6)
  - McClendon, Muriel C., editor, Protestant identities: religion, society, and self-fashioning in post-Reformation England., 1999 (Box 6)
  - McCullough, Kate, 1961-, Regions of identity: the construction of America in women's fiction, 1885-1914., 1999 (Box 7)
  - Menninghaus, Winfried., In praise of nonsense: Kant and Bluebeard., 1999 (Box 7)
  - Meyer, Frederick G. (Frederick Gustav), 1917-, The great herbal of Leonhart Fuchs: De historia stirpium commentarii insignes, 1542 (notable commentaries on the history of plants)., 1999 (Box 7)
  - Michels, Georg Bernhard, At war with the church: religious dissent in seventeenth-century Russia., 1999 (Box 8)
  - Midelfort, H. C. Erik, A history of madness in sixteenth-century Germany., 1999 (Box 8)
  - Midlarsky, Manus I, The evolution of inequality: war, state survival, and democracy in comparative perspective., 1999 (Box 8)
  - Miller, J. Hillis (Joseph Hillis), 1928-, Black holes., 1999 (Box 8)
  - Morris, Stephen J, Why Vietnam invaded Cambodia: political culture and the causes of war., 1999 (Box 8)
  - Nietzsche, Friedrich Wilhelm, 1844-1900, Unpublished writings from the period of Unfashionable observations (Complete works of Friedrich Nietzsche; v. 11)., 1999 (Box 8)
  - Oi, Jean C. and Andrew G. Walder, editors, Property rights and economic reform in China., 1999 (Box 8)
  - Owensby, Brian Philip, 1959-, Intimate ironies: modernity and the making of middle-class lives in Brazil., 1999 (Box 8)
  - Palumbo-Liu, David, Asian/American: historical crossings of a racial frontier., 1999 (Box 8)
  - Patterson, Catherine F., 1963-, Urban patronage in early modern England: corporate boroughs, the landed elite, and the crown, 1580-1640., 1999 (Box 9)
  - Petitot, Jean, et. al, editors, Naturalizing phenomenlogy: issues in contemporary phenomenology and cognitive science., 1999 (Box 9)
  - Rebhun, Linda-Anne, The heart is unknown country: love in the changing economy of northeast Brazil., 1999 (Box 9)
  - Reizbaum, Marilyn, James Joyce's Judaic other., 1999 (Box 9)
  - Reyfman, Irina, Ritualized violence Russian style: the duel in Russian culture and literature., 1999 (Box 9)
  - Rowe, Katherine, Dead hands: fictions of agency, Renaissance to modern., 1999 (Box 9)
  - Sarra, Edith, 1955-, Fictions of femininity: literary inventions of gender in Japanese court women's memoirs., 1999 (Box 9)
  - Sas, Miryam, Fault lines: cultural memory and Japanese surrealism., 1999 (Box 9)
  - Schirmeister, Pamela, 1958-, Less legible meanings: between poetry and philosophy in the work of Emerson., 1999 (Box 10)
  - Schwenger, Peter, 1942-, Fantasm and fiction: on textual envisioning., 1999 (Box 10)
  - Shapira, Anita, Land and power: the Zionist resort to force, 1881-1948., 1999 (Box 10)
  - Shideler, Ross, Questioning the father: from Darwin to Zola, Ibsen, Strindberg, and Hardy., 1999 (Box 10)
  - Sidel, John Thayer, 1966-, Capital, coercion, and crime: bossism in the Philippines., 1999 (Box 10)
  - Siegert, Bernhard, Relays: literature as an epoch of the postal system., 1999 (Box 10)
  - Sivaramakrishnan, K, Modern forests: statemaking and environmental change in colonial Eastern India., 1999 (Box 10)
  - Soares, Joseph A, The decline of privilege: the modernization of Oxford University., 1999 (Box 10)
  - Taussig, Michael T., Defacement: public secrecy and the labor of the negative., 1999 (Box 10)
  - Terrill, Ross, Madame Mao: the white boned demon., 1999 (Box 10)
  - Thorne, Susan, 1958-, Congregational missions and the making of an imperial culture in nineteenth-century England., 1999 (Box 10)
  - Tsin, Michael Tsang-Woon, Nation, governance, and modernity in China: Canton, 1900-1927., 1999 (Box 10)
  - Twinam, Ann, 1946-, Public lives, private secrets: gender, honor, sexuality, and illegitimacy in colonial Spanish America., 1999 (Box 11)
  - Varela, Francisco J., 1946-, Ethical know-how: action, wisdom, and cognition., 1999 (Box 11)
  - Vattimo, Gianni, 1936-, Belief / Gianni Vattimo, translated by Luca D'Isanto and David Webb., 1999 (Box 11)
  - Wagner, Valeria, Bound to act: models of action, dramas of inaction., 1999 (Box 11)
  - Wahl, Elizabeth Susan, Invisible relations: representations of female intimacy in the Age of Enlightenment., 1999 (Box 11)
  - Walker, Kathy Le Mons, Chinese modernity and the peasant path: semicolonialism in the Northern Yangzi Delta., 1999 (Box 11)
  - Wolff, David, 1960-, To the Harbin Station: the liberal alternative in Russian Manchuria, 1898-1914., 1999 (Box 11)
  - Zegart, Amy B., 1967-, Flawed by design: the evolution of the CIA, JCS, and NSC., 1999 (Box 11)
  - Zhang,Yingjin, editor., Cinema and urban culture in Shanghai, 1922-1943., 1999 (Box 11)
- 2000
  - Adorno, Theodor W., 1903-1969, Introduction to sociology., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Adorno, Theodor W., 1903-1969, Metaphysics: concept and problems; edited by Rolf Tiedemann; translated by Edmund Jephcott., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Adorno, Theodor W., 1903-1969, Problems of moral philosophy., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Adorno, Theodor W., 1903-1969, The psychological technique of Martin Luther Thomas' radio addresses., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Allswang, John M, The initiative and referendum in California, 1898-1998., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Badie, Bertrand, The imported state: the westernization of the political order; translated by Claudia Royal., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Baer, Ulrich, Remnants of song: trauma and the experience of modernity in Charles Baudelaire and Paul Celan., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Bardini, Thierry, Bootstrapping: Douglas Engelbart, coevolution, and the origins of personal computing., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Bartky, Ian R, Selling the true time: nineteenth-century timekeeping in America., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Baskes, Jeremy, 1961-, Indians, merchants, and markets: trade and repartimiento production of cochineal dye in late colonial Oaxaca, 1750-1821., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Behlmer, George K. and Fred M. Leventhal, editors, Singular continuities: tradition, nostalgia, and identity in modern British culture., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Bell, Christopher Michael, The Royal Navy, seapower and strategy between the wars., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Berger, Harry, Fictions of the pose: Rembrandt against the Italian Renaissance., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Berger, Harry, The absence of grace: sprezzatura and suspicion in two Renaissance courtesy books., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Berkowitz, Alan J, Patterns of disengagement: the practice and portrayal of reclusion in early medieval China., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Bloch, Ernst, 1885-1977, The spirit of Utopia., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Bonsall, Thomas E, More than they promised: the Studebaker story., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Bourdieu, Pierre, Pascalian meditations / Pierre Bourdieu; translated by Richard Nice., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Boyle, Frank, Swift as nemesis: modernity and its satirist., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Brady, David W., John F. Cogan, and Morris P. Fiorina, editors, Continuity and change in House elections., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Brysk, Alison, 1960-, From tribal village to global village: Indian rights and international relations in Latin America., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Buckler, Julie A, The literary lorgnette: attending opera in imperial Russia., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Bullard, Alice, Exile to paradise: savagery and civilization in Paris and the South Pacific, 1790-1900., 2000 (Box 3)
  - Burrus, Virginia, Begotten, not made: conceiving manhood in late antiquity., 2000 (Box 3)
  - Chen, Yong, 1960-, Chinese San Francisco, 1850-1943: a trans-Pacific community., 2000 (Box 3)
  - Crain, Patricia, The story of A: the alphabetization of America from The New England primer to The scarlet letter., 2000 (Box 3)
  - Crane, Susan A., editor, Museums and memory., 2000 (Box 3)